Contact

eyladson@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/esteen-ladson-barnes-dnp-mpa-rn-ccrn-nea-bc-7811a3a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Patient Safety
BLS

Certifications

Adult Critical Care Nursing
Nurse Executive Advanced-BC

Esteen Ladson Barnes DNP, MPA, RN, CCRN, NEA-BC

Patient Care Director at New York-Presbyterian Hospital Brooklyn, New York

Summary

Experienced Nurse Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Acute Care, Nursing, Inpatient Care, Critical Care, and Hospitals. Strong professional with a Doctor of Nursing Practice focused in Health Systems Leadership from Chamberlain College of Nursing.

Experience

New York-Presbyterian Hospital
Patient Care Director
August 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months)
New York, New York

Maimonides Medical Center
Nurse Manager
December 2014 - August 2017 (2 years 9 months)
SICU and Surgical Progressive Care Unit

The Brooklyn Hospital Center
Nurse Manager
August 2013 - November 2014 (1 year 4 months)
SICU and MICU

Mount Sinai Health System
Nurse Manager
March 2012 - August 2013 (1 year 6 months)
Medical Telemetry

Maimonides Medical Center 8 years 10 months

Assistant Nurse Manager March 2010 - March 2012 (2 years 1 month) Medicine and Progressive Care Units

RN

June 2003 - March 2010 (6 years 10 months)

Cardiothoracic Intensive Care Unit

Education

Chamberlain College of Nursing

Doctor of Nursing Practice, Health Systems Leadership · (2015 - 2017)

St. Joseph's College

Master's degree, Nursing Education · (2008 - 2011)

New York University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1999 - 2003)

NYU Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service Master of Public Administration (MPA), Health Services

Administration · (1994 - 1997)

City University of New York-Herbert H. Lehman College

Bachelor's degree, Computing and Business Management · (1989 - 1991)